Nijat Dursunlu

Front-End Developer



- Baku, Azerbaijan
- +994 51 361 30 25 nicatdursunlu

 - in nijat-dursunlu (H) nicat_dursunlu

Skills

Front-End (React JS, React Router, Redux, Redux Toolkit, TypeScript, Vue JS, Vue Router, Vuex, Vuetify, Material UI, JavaScript(ES5/ES6), HTML, CSS(Sass), Bootstrap, Responsive design)

Version Control Systems (GIT(GitHub, GitLab))

Tools (Jira, Swagger UI, Postman, Slack)

Design (Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD)

Soft skills (Teamwork, Problem solving, Communication, Adaptability, Attention to details, Responsibility, Time Management)

Languages

Azerbaijan

Russian

English

Certificates

• You can see all the certificates I received from the link below [7]

Profile

I have more than a year of experience on Software Development. During this period I did my best with understanding my responsibility and learning required new technologies asap to be part of new projects. It is a priority to me to catch up with deadlines and do my utmost as team member or individually.

Professional Experience

Junior Front-End Developer, ATL Tech ☑

10/2021 - present | Baku, Azerbaijan

- Attending sprints and completing daily tasks
- Projects: Performance Management System, Digital Collection(Dövlət Vergi Xidməti),
- Used tools and technologies: React JS, React Router, Redux Toolkit, Material UI, Vue JS, Vue Router, Vuex, Vuetify, SASS, GitLab, Swagger UI, Jira, Slack

Front-End Developer Intern, ATL Tech □ 04/2021 - 07/2021 | Baku, Azerbaijan

Education

Bachelor / Computer Engineering(ENG),

Baku Engineering University 🗆 09/2017 - 07/2022 | Baku, Azerbaijan

• GPA: 95.63

Courses

Mobile Development,

ABB Tech Academy(DAN IT education) □ 02/2020 - 07/2020 | Baku, Azerbaijan Certificate with Honors 17

References

Vurgun Hajiyev, CTO, ATL Tech Vurgun.Hajiyev@atltech.az, +994 50 286 20 52

Mahammad Sofiyev,

Head of Software Development Department, ATL Tech Mahammad.Sofiyev@atltech.az, +994 50 499 14 69